<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-01-29T00:39:08+04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">My Backpack - Knolling</title><link href="/2025/01/28/backpack-knolling.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Backpack - Knolling" /><published>2025-01-28T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2025-01-28T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>/2025/01/28/backpack-knolling</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/28/backpack-knolling.html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/assets/images/25-1-28-knoll/knoll.png" alt="Picture of my backpack knolling" width="1000" /></p>

<p>These are (most of) the things I carry around in my backpack:</p>

<ol>
  <li>The gigantic 330W power adapter for my laptop and the bag for it</li>
  <li>My Omen laptop, armed with an RTX 3070, as a result of which its battery can last not much more than an hour</li>
  <li>A small power strip and the bag for it, a lifesaver in many situations (especially those invloving the laptop)</li>
  <li>My water bottle, a lifesaver (literally)</li>
  <li>The small bag for my mouse and other computer-related gadgets such as my mobile SSD</li>
  <li>My mouse and mouse pad, necessay as the touchpad of the laptop became glitchy a year back</li>
  <li>Lucas’ Papaw Ointment, very effective as a first-aid medication for small wounds and bites</li>
  <li>A medication for insect bites, quells itchiness very effectively</li>
  <li>FengYouJing, an ointment with colling effects and a strong fragrance that reportedly drives off insects</li>
  <li>My wallet, with some cash and bank card (its exact contents I wish to be kept confidential)</li>
  <li>A folding umbrella, a lifesaver in other regions but probably not here</li>
  <li>An airtag</li>
  <li>Mints for refreshment</li>
  <li>A very light jacket that can be folded and fit into a small pouch</li>
  <li>A Casio FX-991-CN calculator. Fun fact: almost every student from Shanghai has one of these because it is required in the Chinese college entrance exam</li>
  <li>A scissor, comes in handy (sometime unexpectedly)</li>
  <li>A pen bag, for pens, pencils, and handy knickknacks such as a flash drive (and the scissor)</li>
  <li>A large plastic bag. Very unexpectedly useful in many situations especially when you have a scissor</li>
  <li>A high wattage charger</li>
  <li>A small bag for storing all sorts of smaller electronic gadets such as the charger, the powerbank, and some cables</li>
  <li>A 2000 mAh portable powerbank, absolutely necessary for travels</li>
  <li>My backpack (Nearing the end of its life cycle, RIP)</li>
</ol>]]></content><author><name>haoran</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kiwifruit</title><link href="/2018/08/22/kiwifruit.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kiwifruit" /><published>2018-08-22T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2018-08-22T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>/2018/08/22/kiwifruit</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/08/22/kiwifruit.html"><![CDATA[<p>Kiwifruit (often abbreviated as kiwi), or Chinese gooseberry is the
edible berry of several species of woody vines in the genus Actinidia.</p>

<p>The most common cultivar group of kiwifruit is oval, about the size of
a large hen’s egg (5–8 cm (2.0–3.1 in) in length and 4.5–5.5 cm
(1.8–2.2 in) in diameter). It has a fibrous, dull greenish-brown skin
and bright green or golden flesh with rows of tiny, black, edible
seeds. The fruit has a soft texture, with a sweet and unique flavor.</p>]]></content><author><name>ted</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kiwifruit (often abbreviated as kiwi), or Chinese gooseberry is the edible berry of several species of woody vines in the genus Actinidia.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Apples</title><link href="/2018/08/21/apples.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apples" /><published>2018-08-21T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2018-08-21T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>/2018/08/21/apples</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/08/21/apples.html"><![CDATA[<p>An apple is a sweet, edible fruit produced by an apple tree.</p>

<p>Apple trees are cultivated worldwide, and are the most widely grown
species in the genus Malus. The tree originated in Central Asia, where
its wild ancestor, Malus sieversii, is still found today. Apples have
been grown for thousands of years in Asia and Europe, and were brought
to North America by European colonists.</p>]]></content><author><name>jill</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[An apple is a sweet, edible fruit produced by an apple tree.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bananas</title><link href="/2018/08/20/bananas.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bananas" /><published>2018-08-20T00:00:00+04:00</published><updated>2018-08-20T00:00:00+04:00</updated><id>/2018/08/20/bananas</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/08/20/bananas.html"><![CDATA[<p>A banana is an edible fruit – botanically a berry – produced by several
kinds of large herbaceous flowering plants in the genus Musa.</p>

<p>In some countries, bananas used for cooking may be called “plantains”,
distinguishing them from dessert bananas. The fruit is variable in size,
color, and firmness, but is usually elongated and curved, with soft
flesh rich in starch covered with a rind, which may be green, yellow,
red, purple, or brown when ripe.</p>]]></content><author><name>jill</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A banana is an edible fruit – botanically a berry – produced by several kinds of large herbaceous flowering plants in the genus Musa.]]></summary></entry></feed>